{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821337906","data":{"timestamp":" 946821337906"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821338020","data":{"timestamp":" 946821338020"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" dc1ac010-f105-4a7e-98dd-57761b9ef08d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821347325","data":{"timestamp":" 946821347324"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821347709","data":{"timestamp":" 946821347708"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821348205","data":{"timestamp":" 946821348205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821348552","data":{"timestamp":" 946821348551"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821348968","data":{"timestamp":" 946821348968"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821349447","data":{"timestamp":" 946821349447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821349675","data":{"timestamp":" 946821349675"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821352916","data":{"timestamp":" 946821352915"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821352949","data":{"timestamp":" 946821352949"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821353663","data":{"timestamp":" 946821353663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821354074","data":{"timestamp":" 946821354074"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821354374","data":{"timestamp":" 946821354373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821354582","data":{"timestamp":" 946821354582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821354780","data":{"timestamp":" 946821354780"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821355103","data":{"timestamp":" 946821355103"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821355331","data":{"timestamp":" 946821355330"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821358541","data":{"timestamp":" 946821358540"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821358948","data":{"timestamp":" 946821358948"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821361515","data":{"timestamp":" 946821361515"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821361721","data":{"timestamp":" 946821361721"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821361928","data":{"timestamp":" 946821361928"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821365417","data":{"timestamp":" 946821365417"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821369091","data":{"timestamp":" 946821369091"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821370114","data":{"timestamp":" 946821370114"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821372765","data":{"timestamp":" 946821372765"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821373138","data":{"timestamp":" 946821373137"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821373622","data":{"timestamp":" 946821373621"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821373966","data":{"timestamp":" 946821373965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821374370","data":{"timestamp":" 946821374370"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821374843","data":{"timestamp":" 946821374843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821375067","data":{"timestamp":" 946821375066"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821378259","data":{"timestamp":" 946821378259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821378293","data":{"timestamp":" 946821378293"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821379006","data":{"timestamp":" 946821379006"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821379401","data":{"timestamp":" 946821379401"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821379694","data":{"timestamp":" 946821379694"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821379898","data":{"timestamp":" 946821379898"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821380093","data":{"timestamp":" 946821380092"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821380406","data":{"timestamp":" 946821380406"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821380629","data":{"timestamp":" 946821380629"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821383282","data":{"timestamp":" 946821383282"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821383351","data":{"timestamp":" 946821383351"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" f6c36ae0-f9bd-4105-849c-47fc0f145940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821418495","data":{"timestamp":" 946821418495"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 9a743446-f8e1-434c-8287-6ebd49a3a07b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821441730","data":{"timestamp":" 946821441730"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 9a743446-f8e1-434c-8287-6ebd49a3a07b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821455099","data":{"timestamp":" 946821455099"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 9a743446-f8e1-434c-8287-6ebd49a3a07b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821469786","data":{"timestamp":" 946821469786"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 9a743446-f8e1-434c-8287-6ebd49a3a07b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 4"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821478353","data":{"timestamp":" 946821478352"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 9a743446-f8e1-434c-8287-6ebd49a3a07b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..4.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821499201","data":{"timestamp":" 946821499200"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_D_Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821505906","data":{"timestamp":" 946821505906"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_S_H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821512591","data":{"timestamp":" 946821512591"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821519245","data":{"timestamp":" 946821519243"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_L_CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821525887","data":{"timestamp":" 946821525887"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_I_S"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821532531","data":{"timestamp":" 946821532531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_L_A"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821539172","data":{"timestamp":" 946821539172"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_L_K"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821545863","data":{"timestamp":" 946821545863"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_B_H"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821552523","data":{"timestamp":" 946821552523"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_W_L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821559223","data":{"timestamp":" 946821559221"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_U_Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:L..L.all.10.rand.say.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821572375","data":{"timestamp":" 946821572374"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 82dd8a96-701d-4967-a25d-b6ee7ee289aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_L..L.all.10.rand.say.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_L_U_Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821640289","data":{"timestamp":" 946821640289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 8d5559a0-7fa8-4f7f-b6a5-95f9dbeec1f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huo_pale-fisi-zake-huo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" huo"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821645856","data":{"timestamp":" 946821645856"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 8d5559a0-7fa8-4f7f-b6a5-95f9dbeec1f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huo_pale-fisi-zake-huo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" huo"," userResponse":" huo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821691558","data":{"timestamp":" 946821691558"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 8d5559a0-7fa8-4f7f-b6a5-95f9dbeec1f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" huo_pale-fisi-zake-huo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821691642","data":{"timestamp":" 946821691642"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" 8d5559a0-7fa8-4f7f-b6a5-95f9dbeec1f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi imetuacha?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMETUACHA"," userResponse":" IMETUACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821701973","data":{"timestamp":" 946821701973"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821707695","data":{"timestamp":" 946821707695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821713402","data":{"timestamp":" 946821713402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821718062","data":{"timestamp":" 946821718062"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821722985","data":{"timestamp":" 946821722985"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821728404","data":{"timestamp":" 946821728404"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821732874","data":{"timestamp":" 946821732874"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821738216","data":{"timestamp":" 946821738216"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821742406","data":{"timestamp":" 946821742406"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821745777","data":{"timestamp":" 946821745777"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821750249","data":{"timestamp":" 946821750249"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821755062","data":{"timestamp":" 946821755062"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821758392","data":{"timestamp":" 946821758392"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821761686","data":{"timestamp":" 946821761686"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821765584","data":{"timestamp":" 946821765584"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821770756","data":{"timestamp":" 946821770756"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821774939","data":{"timestamp":" 946821774938"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821779650","data":{"timestamp":" 946821779650"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821783543","data":{"timestamp":" 946821783543"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821787606","data":{"timestamp":" 946821787606"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821791062","data":{"timestamp":" 946821791062"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821794620","data":{"timestamp":" 946821794619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821798392","data":{"timestamp":" 946821798392"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821804954","data":{"timestamp":" 946821804954"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821810730","data":{"timestamp":" 946821810729"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821817202","data":{"timestamp":" 946821817201"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_165515"," gameId":" fa50b7da-a83b-4e05-aee5-bc8ad45a7cc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}